Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers MSS.156
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize
  - Series VII: Printed Materials
    - Adirondacks map, undated; cuid23190 (Box 17, Folder 848)
    - Everglades Echo, 1984; cuid23191 (Box 17, Folder 855)
    - New York Nichiben, 1989; cuid23192 (Box 17, Folder 866A)
    - Ruby Dam Quadrangle map, undated; cuid23193 (Box 17, Folder 874)
- Mapcase
  - Series I Subseries B: Colab Shows and Events
    - Talk is Cheap street posters, 1984; cuid23194 (Folder 10)
    - Real Estate Show, 1979-2014; cuid23208 (Folder 1)
  - Series II Subseries B: Andrea Callard Artist Files 1973-1976, 150 Chambers St.
    - Two long drawings. Brown paper and brown ink., 1973-1976; cuid23195 (Folder 11)
  - Series II Subseries E: Andrea Callard Artist Files, 1982-1986 Lispenard St
    - Poster advertisement for "Central America Flowers from the Volcano". Sponsored in part by Colab. Andrea Callard poster., 1984; cuid23196 (Folder 12)
  - Series IV Subseries B: Other Artist Files, Collaborations and Group Shows
    - Chart created by Reese and Winnie Williams, undated; cuid23197 (Folder 14)